{
    "id": "7420d895233f4030bd2da3dacd45ce29",
    "title": "Omission of that exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f4c97a003d7e479494ac40c46d146cee",
            "title": "Omission Of That",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I knew ………………………. didn’t want to help me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she",
                        "that she",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susie said ………………….. was feeling better.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she",
                        "that she",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. should forget me so quickly was rather a shock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "That she",
                        "She",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. she was a minor made it difficult for her to get a job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "The fact",
                        "The fact that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "James replied ……………………….. was doing fine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "that he",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He shouted ………………………… was busy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "that he",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Many people had disagreed with the Copernicus’ view ……………………… revolved round the sun.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "the earth",
                        "that the earth",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I thought …………………. were in Singapore.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you",
                        "that you",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was surprised ………………….. didn’t come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she",
                        "that she",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He spoke in a low voice so ………………………. wouldn’t wake up the baby.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "that he",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}